Jackson Lee

Full Stack Blockchain Developer



Passionate and skilled Full-stack Blockchain and Web Developer offering 7 years of developing experience. Specialize in building smart contracts, trading platforms, and dApps in Ethereum and Solana Network, and developing Web Applications in MERN and Laravel.

Experience

2020 - Present

NFT Specialist | Freelance

Remote Job, Toronto

- Generating artworks and metadata
- Deploying artworks and metadata onto Arweave through metaplex upload
- Deploying candy machine through metaplex
- Developing landing page
- Developing minting page and integrating with metaplex
- Configuring start date and timer Ethereum
- Generating artworks and metadata
- Deploying artworks and metadata onto ipfs/pinata
- Creating smart contract and deploying onto Ethereum
- Developing landing page
- Developing minting page and integrating with the contract
- Configuring start date and timer
- Opensea configuration: registration, integrating placeholder

2018 - 2019

Blockchain Developer

Daytona, Sweden Developed various kinds of tokens including ERC-20, ERC-721, BEP-20, and smart contracts for DApp.

- ERC-721 NFT for game characters
- Game backend smart contracts in Solidity
- Fungible tokens for games
- Built Cryptocurrency Exchange/Trading System, Defi, Gambling
- Participated in Trading platforms and NFT staking platform development



Skills

Languages

Solidity C++ Javascript Typescript HTML5 CSS PHP7

Web

ReactJS
Redux, Hook
Angular
Laravel
Express, Nodejs
Bootstrap4, 5

Blockchain

Smart Contract Truffle Hardhat Openzepplin Web3.js Ether.js ERC-20, ERC-721, BEP-20

Test

Mocha Jest Karma

2016 - 2018

Full-stack Developer

Daytona, Sweden

- Frontend development using React/Angular
- Collaborating and co-developing with React/Laravel
- Implemented custom front end designs and user experience
- Full stack development using MERN stack
- Developed Web applications and Websites from scratch to Complete including front end and back end
- Extensive knowledge on full Application development life cycle, MVC, Modular structure wiring, and workflow from scratch to productions.

2015 - 2016

Lead Front-end Engineer

Daytona, Sweden

- Completely redesigned the landing page—resulting to a 30% conversion rate increase.
- Built from scratch the back-office—leading to a huge productivity boost compared to the previous Trello-based system.
- Developed and implemented solar module installation designing tool

Education

2011 - 2015

Bachelor of Computer Science

YORK UNIVERSITY

My most memorable moment was the first week of my undergraduate degree. To see the vast and abundant student groups and organizations displayed throughout YorkU campus welcoming new students made me feel as if I had arrived at a true bastion of diversity not just of academics, but of thought and ideals. That scene of the sprawling student group booths like many single communities coming together to paint a mosaic of diversity were a perfect reflection of the diaspora that inhabits the city of Toronto.

2009 - 2011

High School

ROSEMOUNT HIGH SCHOOL.

Rosemount High School is an English-language high school located in Montreal, Quebec, Canada. It opened in 1951. The school offers a special music program as well as drama and visual arts programs. Today, the school offers a French-immersion program in addition to its English core program

Contact

- ★ Toronto, Canada
- G+ goldenblcdev@gmail.com
- **1** +1(931) 361 1910